Guide to the Living Stage records 1965-2001
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 3: Audiovisual materials, 1967-1998
  - Reel to Reel Materials, 1977-1985
    - Performance SK #7, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Performance SK #8, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Performance SR #4, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Performance SR #5, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Performance SR #6, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Rebecca Rice VO, January 12, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Rehearsal SR #1, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Rehearsal SR #2, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Rehearsal SR #3, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Runaways - Pulls from Rolls 5-8, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Runaways - PX #1, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Runaways - PX #2, November 28, 1980 (Box 98)
    - Runaways - PX #3, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Runaways - PX #4, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Runaways - PX #5, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Runaways - PX #6, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Runaways - PX #8, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Runaways - Rolls 1-4, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box XL Box, Folder 15)
      XL Roll
    - Runaways - RX #7, November 28, 1980 (Box 98)
    - Seniors CR 1-3, January 30, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Seniors CR 3-5, January 30, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Seniors CR 5-7, January 30, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - SR # 10, November 28, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - St. Mary's, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - St. Mary's R-1 and 2, January 30, 1981 (Box 98)
    - St. Mary's R-3 Pix, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - St. Mary's Trims, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Susan Pix, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - TBBNS - "Its Your World" CR18, January 30, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - TBBNS - #6 CR-9, January 30, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - TBBNS - #9 CR-18, January 30, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Teens - Pulls from Rolls 3, 4, 5, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Teens - Pulls from Rolls 6, 7, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Teens - Pulls from Rolls 8, 9, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Teens CR 13 #7, January 30, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Teens CR 13 #8, January 30, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Teens CR 3-5, January 30, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Teens CR 5-8, January 30, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Teens PX #1, January 30, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Teens PX #2, January 30, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Teens PX #4, January 30, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Teens PX #5, January 30, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Teens PX #6, January 30, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Teens PX #7 "Ballou", January 30, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Unnamed Reel, January 26, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Cassette and VHS Tapes, 1978-1998
    - A.U [American University] Thoughts of the Actors on Process of Faces of Fascism - Gregg, Rebecca, March 18, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 28)
      Tape 3 of 3
    - A.U [American University] FOF [Faces of Fascism] Process Discussion, March 18, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 26)
      Tape 1 of 3
    - A.U [American University] FOF [Faces of Fascism] Process Discussion, March 18, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 27)
      Tape 2 of 3
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 1, Tape 1, Robert Alexander, January 21, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      Cassette Tape
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 1, Tape 2, Robert Alexander, January 21, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 10, Tape 19, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 10, Tape 20, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 11, Tape 21, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 11, Tape 22, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 12, Tape 23, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 12, Tape 24, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 2, Tape 4, Robert Alexander, January 28, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 3, Tape 5, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 3, Tape 6, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 4, Tape 7, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 4, Tape 8, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 5, Tape 10, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 5, Tape 9, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 6, Tape 11, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 6, Tape 12, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 7, Tape 13, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 7, Tape 14, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 8, Tape 15, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 8, Tape 16, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 9, Tape 17, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - American University - Improvisational Theatre for the Classroom - Session 9, Tape 18, circa 1980s (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - American University - L.S Performance - Session 9, Tape 1, April 1, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - American University - L.S Performance - Session 9, Tape 2, April 1, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - ADASA Jams Dub Original Master, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - ADASA Jams Orig, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - ADASA Rap Tape with Takes, December 1987 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - ADASA Rap Tapes with Takes, December 1987 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - CSP Rap Master, 1980s (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - CSP Rap Original, 1980s (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Freedom Rap, December 1985 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Freedom Rap, December 1985 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Hope Rap - CSP, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Hope Rap - CSP, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Rap on Violence, December 1987 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Rap on Violence, December 1987 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Violence - ADASA, December 1987 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - ADASA Edited Original, 1990-1991 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      Betamax
    - ADASA (edited version), December 1990 - May 1991 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      VHS
    - ADASA Tape 1, 1986-1987 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - American University (A.U) Course - Bob A. in class, April 15, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      Beta Tape 1 of 2
    - American University (A.U) Course - Bob A. in class, April 15, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      Beta Tape 2 of 2
    - And Always There's the Rainbow, circa 1980s or 1990s (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - And Always There's the Rainbow (3 Segments), circa late 1980s (Box 102, Folder 7)
      U-matic
    - And Always There's the Rainbow Beta #2, circa 1980s or 1990s (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Bell Multicultural Rap Session, circa 1980s and 1990s (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Birthday Wishes, 1995-1996 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Breakfast Piece, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Capital Edition, April 5, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Catherine Irwin "City Council Speech", March 7, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - CSP Video 1, 1988-1989 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - CSP Video 2, 1988-1989 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - End of the Year Interview with Roland and Barnes (ADASA), August 5, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Every Heart In the House, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Fairhill Tape #2 Complete, January 21, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - First Lady Benefit, March 16, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Garrison I and II, 1994-1995 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Halima's Newspaper Piece, "The Hubble" and Halima's Peter Pan Monologue, November 11, 1990 and March 13, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Happy Birthday from John - Happy 30th Birthday from Red Ladder Co, 1995-1996 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Hasbro Piece - Two Takes, November 10, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - IHAD, Summer 1989 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Images, June 1986 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - India, Cathy's Baby, The Next 2000, Aliens, Can't Trust Them, Grown, 1992-1993 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Koba I and II and Garrison, 1993-1994 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Living Lecture Series - Robert Alexander: Healing Society Through Artistic Creativity, November 17, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Living Stage Documentary, May 29, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Living Stage Documentary, circa 1980s and 1990s (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Living Stage Theatre, 1989-1991 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Longstreet, June 1986 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Lynched Hopes and Unsung Songs, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Mental Health, circa late 1980s (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Misc Groups Rehearsals - Garrison I and II, Koba, IHAD, TMOT, 1992-1993 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Myths Rehearsal - Characters, Singer, Poet, Sculpture, October 8, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Nathea on DC Today - Return to Kelly, November 18, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Off the Fence on America's Voice, April 14, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Pieces II, 1986-1987 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - PPIHWP Compelation (sic), 1997 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Project Unite, circa 1980s and 1990s (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Rebecca - Les' Song, circa 1980s and 1990s (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Sharpe Health, January 3, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Sharpe Health Olympics, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Stockholm Residency - Educational Broadcasting Co., May 14, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Strange, Bitter Crop PCP (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Teen Mothers, circa 1980s and 1990s (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - The Root of Rage, circa 1980s and 1990s (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Theatre in Washington, November 26, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Think About the Children, April 30, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Think About the Children, April 30, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Violence and the Public Response - Indiana Criminologists Colloquium, Indiana State University, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - WETA, circa late 1980s (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - WETA - Theatre of the Heart, circa late 1980s (Box 106, Folder 6)